[Music]
[Música]
eh move let's see the discussion okay
eh movida a ver lo de la tertulia vale
eh Fran Okay but what's
eh Fran Okay pero qué
happening is that it lasts an hour and a half what
pasa que dura una hora y media lo que ha
this guy has uploaded what parts do I see what
subido este tío qué partes veo qué
parts do I see nobody brought it dude everything
partes veo ninguno lo ha trado tío todo
but I'm not going to watch for an hour and a half what
pero no voy a ver una hora y media qué
part do I see dude Okay let's see the
parte veo tío Bueno vamos a ver el papel
toilet paper what for To put bandages on
higiénico para qué Para poner vendas a
animals no but tomy had it the
los animales no pero tomy lo tenía el
other day Look tomy you can see tomy Yeah
otro día a Mira tomy a tomy se le ve Sí
but it's because he'll have to tie it up
pero es porque tendrá que atarlo
I'm innovating I also have some
yo estoy innovando También tengo unos
cotton swabs here but let's see they have been
cotonetes aquí pero a ver ellos han sido
critical of miar's video I understand
críticos con el vídeo de miar entiendo
no I mean Fran was pissed off with
no O sea el Fran estaba [__] con
some of cell's reactions because
algunas reacciones del cell porque por
apparently he had eaten some things
lo visto se había comido algunas cosas
from the video but of course Cell wasn't there at
del vídeo pero claro es que Cell no
the time he was he arrived
estaba en la época él estaba el llegó
later I mean I understand that it's understandable that
después O sea entiendo que se entiendo
maybe he doesn't know some things from
que a lo mejor no sepa algunas cosas de
back then the lord in fact I doubt
de aquel entonces el lores de hecho dudo
that Tommy knows much the lord is here
que Tommy sepa mucho el lores sea aquí
those of us who know about lords nauter gibel
los que sabemos de lores nauter gibel
who was a fan Sur tartaja I don't think so either
que era fan Sur tartaja creo que tampoco
eh talaja arrived later I don't know  what to
eh talaja llego después no sé qué
tell you about talaja if the Lore will taste good
deciros de talaja si sabrá el Lore bien
or not To put less in the urethra
o no Para meter menos en la uretra una
once the act is finished you see that
vez terminado el acto ves eso que
brigand are not cotton I don't know what it's
brigante no son coton no sé cómo se
called in your country Ah
llama en su país Ah
swabs swabs tip if in the
bastoncillos bastoncillos tip si en la
head I feel like we're going to get
cabeza para siento que nos vamos a penar
beaten up or what preferably It's
de hostias o qué preferentemente Es
probably nothing it's not likely either let's see they
probable nada tampoco es probable a ver
know they finish the salt clips that are
saben que acaban la sal clips que nos
going to all of us you know for sure they're going to come out let's
van a a todos sab seguro que van a salir
see what happens we enter but we enter the
a ver qué pasa entramos pero entramos en
subject there but
materia de ahí pero
1900 is the Prim But how did it enter
1900 es la Prim Pero cómo fue que entró
or rather why did it happen is that nter has
o sea por qué se terció es que nter
never been never has never been
nunca se ha nunca se ha nunca se ha
put there in the image it wasn't the
puesto ahí en la imagen no era la
discussion I once that that
tertulia yo alguna vez que que eso no
was not part of the discussion at the beginning it's not the
era de la tertulia al principio no es la
first real interaction in video call
primera interacción real en videollamada
between nauter and Frank when Fran came here I do
entre nauter y Frank cuando vino aquí
n't think there was eh No
Fran tampoco estaba creo eh No
either no no these four
tampoco no no estaban estos cuatro
fish were there we were and he fought with
pescaos estábamos nosotros y peleó con
tataj we looked and said
tataj nosotros mirábamos y decíamos
Who no who no He's a son of a [ __ ]
Quién no quien no Es un hijo de [__]
for you let's see I think that for  make
para ti a ver yo creo que para hacer
gossip and to do the job that
salseo y para hacer el trabajo que
all of you who make gossip do
hacéis todos los que hacéis salseo
have to be a bit of a son of a [ __ ]
tienen que ser un poco hijos de [__]
because you have to stick your finger in
porque tienes que meter el dedo a ve en
people you like, people
gente que te cae bien en gente que
you have a good affinity with, it's normal you want to
tienes buena afinidad es normal quieres
browse the internet safely and
Navegar de forma segura en internet y
also access all the content of
además acceder a todo el contenido de
your favorite platforms like Netflix,
tus plataformas favoritas como Netflix
HBO Max, or Disney Plus cyberg VPN And I do
hbo Max o Disney Plus cyberg VPN Y es
n't know if you know but there is
que no sé si lo sabes pero hay
content that is not available in your country
contenidos que en tu país no están
and with this little trick you can
disponibles y con este truquillo puedes
access all the content wherever you
acceder a todo el contenido estés donde
are, I don't know if you know what a VPN is
estés no sé si sabes lo que es una VPN
but it's an extension that you put on your
pero es una extensión que le pones a tu
internet with which you mask your IP and
internet con la que en mascaras la IP y
apart from browsing completely safely and
aparte de Navegar completamente seguro y
anonymously without anyone being able to know who you
anónimo sin que nadie pueda saber quién
are and where you are, it can be used to access
eres y dónde estás sirve para acceder a
some content that is blocked
algunos contenidos que están bloqueados
in your country there are movies and series on your
en tu país hay películas y series en tus
favorite platforms that are not
plataformas favoritas que no están
available there are television programs,
disponibles hay programas de televisión
for example, in media set content that
por ejemplo en medias set contenidos que
if you try to watch them outside of Spain
si los intentas ver fuera de España
they have a geoblock that doesn't
tienen un geobloqueo que no te lo
allow it Well, with cyberghost VPN that's
permite Pues con cyberghost VPN eso se
over Apart from being protected by
acabó Aparte de estar protegido
browsing anonymously you will be able to
navegando bajo el anonimato podrás
access  to the contents of the entire
acceder a los contenidos de todo el
planet you will also have Total privacy
planeta además tendrás privacidad Total
since it keeps your connection private and
ya que mantiene tu conexión en privado y
protects your data ultra-fast speed
protege tus datos velocidad ultrarápida
to eliminate the lake in any
para eliminar el lago en cualquier juego
online game with which you can enjoy
online con los que podrás disfrutar de
live broadcasts without interruptions and as I have already
directos sin interrupciones y como ya os
told you Freedom to access all the
he dicho Libertad para acceder a todo el
content on the planet wherever and whenever
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
you want also take advantage of the 83
quieras además aprovecha son 83 de
discount using the link that I
descuento utilizando el enlace que te
leave you in the description of this video and be careful
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
because you can try cyberg VPN 45
ojo porque puedes probar cyberg VPN 45
days without obligation and if you are not convinced you
días sin compromiso y si no te convence
ask for a refund and it will return it to you in the
pides el reembolso y te devuelve en la
pass so do not wait any longer to
pasa así que no esperes más para
protect your connection and increase your
proteger tu conexión y aumentar tu
internet experience run to click on the
experiencia en internet corre al click
link in the description and take advantage of
al enlace de la descripción y aprovecha
this super cyberg VPN offer to
esta super oferta cyberg VPN para
browse completely free and secure that is to
navegar completamente libre y seguro es
say, for example, I have a
decir yo por ejemplo tengo contigo una
bad mood with you one day and the
una mala [__] un día y al día
next day I see another video and I like it, I
siguiente veo otro vídeo y me gusta es
mean, hey, the work that you do is not
decir eh el trabajo que hacéis no es no
easy because you can't Let's see, you
es fácil porque no podéis A ver os
can abstain For example, if someone
podéis abstener Por ejemplo si alguien
says something about the south, ask the south to [ __ ] the
dice algo del sur le pidan al sur que
cousin of I don't know about a
sea follado a la prima de no sé de un
friend and well it happened that they came
amigo y bueno ha pasado que han venido
here they came here to with stories
aquí han venido aquí a a con historias
of romances and rolls and things and
de romances y rollos y cosas y
obviously the one who has the one who has
evidentemente el que tiene el que tiene
hand is free from the one of the funa does not p
mano se libra de la de la funa no le p
screen obviously You're going to try to omit
pantal obviamente Vais a intentar omitir
the subject a little to say Well yes it goes like
un poco el tema para decir Bueno sí va
this well what I do with Dallas is to
tal pues lo que hago yo con Dallas es
say when you have a friend you have to
decir cuando tú tienes un amigo tú
lower the intensity Frank
tienes que que bajar la intensidad Frank
came up because they wouldn't stop saying it I
subió porque ellos no dejaban de decirlo
mean Frank they were talking yesterday
o sea Frank ellos estaban hablando ayer
the art of the subject no And then Fran
la ctura del tema no Y entonces Fran
was listening like he is all [ __ ]
estaba escuchando como está todo el [__]
day listening to all the [ __ ] gossip of everyone [ __ ]
día escuchando todo el [__] salseo de
no and appeared there
todo el [__] mundo no y apareció por ahí
I'm going to have a chat with Fran eh I
yo voy a hacer una tertulia con Fran eh
'm going to have a chat with Fran I mean I
voy a hacer una tertulia con Fran o sea
have no problem saying the things
yo no tengo problema en decir las cosas
that Dallas does wrong or that I consider
que hace mal Dallas o que yo Considero
Dallas does wrong or Javi or whoever
que hace mal Dallas o Javi o quien sea
no but your job is a [ __ ]
no pero el trabajo vuestro es una putada
because sometimes you have to stick your
porque es que a veces tenéis que meter
finger in people that you like I mean
el dedo a gente que os cae bien Es decir
who tells you that so and so he doesn't do something
quién te dice a ti que y va no hace algo
or that gre doesn't do something wrong and you stick your
o que gre no hace algo malo y le metéis
finger in and say [ __ ] This is going to
el dedo y decís [__] Esto me va a
affect me for the es me  you understand it's
afectar para los es me entendéis es que
a [ __ ] I mean I understand I
una putada O sea yo lo entiendo yo me
can get mad any day with
puedo cabrear cualquier día con
any of you and with dasas no m well we
cualquiera de vosotros y con el dasas no
will invite him from time to time
m pues lo invitaremos de vez en cuando
Of course I understand I don't know the truth but it
Claro entiendo no lo sé la verdad pero
's normal Why Because I laugh
es lo normal Por qué Porque yo me río
when nauter makes a video of whoever
cuando nauter hace un vídeo de quien sea
but when it's my turn I say what a son
pero cuando me toca a mí digo qué hijo
of a [ __ ] the [ __ ] is I burst you
de [__] el [__] es lo reviento
understand I mean it's like that but at the end of the
entiendes o sea es así pero al final del
day it's me I me I don't know I'm a
día es yo que me yo me no sé yo soy un
little more soca when I make a video I let's
poco más soca yo cuando me hac en vídeo
see no no no I don't know if I've
me me lo A ver no no no no sé si he
seen all all all the videos that they've
visto todos todos todos los vídeos que
made to me but I honestly it
me han hecho a mí pero yo sinceramente
's something that gives I take it as I
es una cosa que da yo me lo tomo a me
laugh it's that in the end it's not my
río sea es que al final final no es mi
life the internet you understand let's see
vida el internet me entiendes a ver te
something could bother you Or you can say you
puede molestar algo O puedes decir t
turkey what does this turkey say you know but I don't I don't
pavo qu dice este pavo sabes pero no me
know I'm lying and for the Latino who
lo no sé imiento y para el latino que
are by nature gossips because it's
somos por por naturaleza cotillas porque
in our culture well [ __ ] I
está en nuestra cultura pues [__] yo
used to listen to the radio all my life
antes escuchaba la radio toda la vida
now I go around with the phone in my
ahora yo voy con el teléfono en el
pocket all day doing things I've been
bolsillo todo el día haciendo cosas yoos
listening from the beginning I
estado escuchando desde el principio
was doing things and it's
estaba haciendo cosas y y es
pure entertainment at the end of the
entretenimiento puro y duro al final del
day what happens is that a lot of people don't
día lo que pasa es que mucha gente no
understand that one thing is the show
entiende que una cosa es el espectáculo
that is put on here and then well, when I meet up,
que se hace aquí y luego pues que yo me
like when I met
encuentre pues como cuando me encontré
Dallas, eh what am I going to say, I'll kill you, we'll have
con Dallas eh qué le voy a decir te mato
a coffee. I meet up
no nos tomamos un café Yo me encuentro
with Nauter eh in Madrid or wherever and I'm
con el nauter eh en Madrid o donde sea y
not going to tell him you son of a [ __ ] I'm going to
no le voy a decir hijo de [__] te voy a
kill you, I mean, damn Nauter, you see if you
matar es decir [__] nauter por lo ves si
say [ __ ] we'll have a coffee, I
dices hostias nos tomamos un café es
mean, you have to differentiate very well what
decir hay que diferenciar muy bien lo
is work, what you do here, and what
que es el trabajo lo que haces aquí y lo
is your personal life, you understand. And if you
que es la vida personal entiendes Y si
want to dedicate yourself to gossip, it can't
te quieres dedicar al salseo no puede
be, eh, a soul of Charity, you can't. I
ser eh Un alma de la Caridad no puedes O
mean, you can't, you can't. I mean, you watch the
sea no puedes no puedes O sea tú ves los
videos, you see Tomy, but when Tomy
vídeos de ves a tomy pero cuando tomy
makes a video, it can blow your
hace un vídeo te puede reventar la
mind, and then you watch it and he doesn't say anything, and then your
cabeza y luego lo ves y no dice nada y
hair comes out here and he
luego te viene el pelos sucio aquí y te
sets you up, I'm telling you, it's not our fault, it's not our fault, it's their fault
la monta te digo no es culpa nuestra no
for
es culpa nuestra es culpa de ellos por
being such an [ __ ] and making their life their
ser tan [__] y hacer su vida sus
problems and their fights public, of course  you
problemas y sus peleitas públicas claro
account m everything that is public
cuentas m todo lo que es público se
can be criticized literally what
puede criticar literalmente lo que
you said is what Frank says the one who says that
dijiste es lo que dice Frank el que lo
to me is that sincerely Look,
de que a mí es que sinceramente Mira a
obviously there will be things that
ver evidentemente habrá cosas que
cross the line you know I mean I don't mean
traspasen la línea sabes O sea no quiero
with this that I like being
decir con esto que me gusta que me
called an abuser pedophile I don't know I don't know
llamen maltratador pedófilo no sé no sé
how much you know but like I know m I have
cuánto sabes pero en plan yo que sé m Yo
seen videos that we have seen here I
hay vídeos que hemos visto aquí yo me
laugh I mean you can't disappear from the
río O sea tú no puedes desaparecer del
map or rather the fact that you generate and that what
mapa o sea el hecho de que tú generes e
you what what
que se comente lo que tú lo que lo que
you think what you don't think is commented on because Look,
tú piensas lo que no piensas porque Mira
Javi Look if Dallas does this he
es que el Javi Mira si hace Dallas esto
says this and yes and if an enemy does it he
dice esto y si y si lo hace un enemigo
says the other thing I mean it's that people
dice lo otro o sea es que a la gente le
care about what you think and what you
importa lo que tú piensas y lo que tú
say you understand So to me
dices me entiendes Entonces a mí
sincerely I do like that they
sinceramente a mí sí me cae simpático
make videos about me And that thing and this is you
que me hagan vídeos Y esa movida y está
know what I'm telling you Look at this we saw it
sabes lo que te digo Mira esto lo vimos
no Ah yes of course we reacted here we
no Ah sí claro esto reaccionamos aquí
have excerpts you know we have laughed
tenemos extractos sabes nos hemos reído
with with with the criticism of do you remember the one who
con con con la crítica de os acordáis
said that I got involved
ese que decía que que yo me metía
eh  that I was getting into chasca do you remember that one we
eh que yo me metía a chasca os acordáis
saw that one yes we have a
de ese que vimos ese sí tenemos una
reaction what is this Javi Oliveira
reacción qué es esto Javi oliveira
defends Aguel from his lawyer I don't
defiende a aguel de su abogado yo no me
take it badly the truth what happens is that
lo tomo a mal la verdad lo que pasa es
when it's your turn Tomy when it's your turn
que cuando te toca a ti tomy cuando
as a
cuando te toca a ti como
person I mean [ __ ] life why but it
persona es decir [__] vida por qué pero
's because of the ego because of the ego that
es por el ego por el ego que tenemos
all of us who are in the
todos los que estamos dentro del mundo
entertainment world have I mean those of us who are
del espectáculo es decir los que somos
famous let's say that we are I am
famosos vamos a decir que som yo soy
famous it pisses you off because you always want to
famoso te jode porque tú quieres siempre
have everything framed in a
tener todo enmarcado en un en un cuadro
pretty picture and when they come out with something that's
bonito y cuando te salen con algo que es
ugly it pisses off your ego It's normal What happens is
feo te jode al ego Es lo normal Qué pasa
that then you close the computer me here I
que luego cierras el ordenad yo aquí
close the computer and I laugh at
Cierro la computadora y me descojono de
everyone because look eh I live happily I
todo el mundo porque mira eh vivo feliz
live in peace but that ego of the famous person
vivo en paz pero ese ego del del famoso
there's no way to control it I mean you
no hay manera de controlarlo es decir tú
can say that it's no no no it doesn't affect me
puedes decir que es no no no me afecta a
everyone God affects everyone God
todo Dios le afecta a todo Dios le
affects them you understand So eh You have two
afecta entiendes Entonces eh Tienes dos
options either you retire from this
opciones o te retiras de esto de la vida
public life or you have to put up with it And if you
pública o te tienes que aguantar Y si la
screw up damn it  you've screwed up if
cagas [__] pues lo has cagado si
you know it's something so direct that [ __ ] you
teón es algo tan directo que [__]
're hooked I'm hooked on
estás enganchado Yo estoy enganchado a
all the I eat because I have to do
todas las Yo como como tengo que hacer
a lot of things and walk and such I go all
muchas cosas y caminar y tal yo voy todo
[ __ ] day with the phone on and
el [__] día con el teléfono encendido y
if I'm not listening
si no estoy
to Javi, I mean listening to Javi Well maybe he
a Javi o sea escuchando a Javi Pues a lo
gets on the phone because of the schedules and
mejor se mete el cel por los horarios y
and I listen to the phone you know I mean or to
y escucho al cel me entiendes o sea o a
anyone it could be anyone when it
cualquiera puede ser cualquiera cuando
arrives it's it's a form of
llega es es Es una modalidad de
entertainment that a lot of people protest
entretenimiento que mucha gente protesta
all the big streamers say the
todos los streamers grandes dicen el
gossip the gossip everyone has their
salseo el salseo todo el mundo tiene su
way of doing things and above
su manera de hacer las cosas y sobre
all you know because because yoy I don't
todo su conoces porque porque yoy yo no
go Looking at people and it comes to you
voy Mirando a la gente y te viene te
like Ah I am I don't know who Ah [ __ ] of a
dice Ah soy no sé quién Ah [__] de
[ __ ] you understand in what we know here I do
[__] entiendes en lo que conocemos aquí
n't depend on anyone to say [ __ ] he's
no depend de nadie de decir [__] está
putting pressure so that I don't talk about
metiendo presión para que no hable de
this or that the pressure is on
este o del otro la presión noos la
you guys who's been here who's been
metéis vosos que lleva aquí que lleva
here for 8 minutes giving lectures I
aquí el abuelo 8 minutos dando cátedra o
mean the grandfather has been here for 8 minutes
sea lleva aquí el abuelo 8 minutos
giving these people a lecture and they're
echándole el serón a esta gente y están
all there listening he looks like a teacher
todos ahí escuchando parece un profe
But when  they get into the subject
Pero cuándo entran en la en la materia
potentially dangerous dog that if you don't
perro potencialmente peligroso que si no
have authority with the dog he gave him that he
tienes autoridad con el perro le dio que
was rolled and you hit him with the
estaba enrollado y le dabas con el
newspaper in the ass you understand me I mean it
periódico en el culo me entiendes o sea
's the people here take things like
es la gente aquí coge las cosas como
look he said a slap Well if we
fíjate ha dicho una [__] Bueno si
all have to speak with a
tenemos que hablar todos con un lenguaje
normal language eh [ __ ] If all the streamers
normal eh [__] Si todos los streamers
who criticize that would have to take a
que critican eso se tendría que hacer un
good editing course to learn to
un buen curso de edición para aprender a
speak you understand eh each one
hablar entiendes eh cada uno que
understands what they want but but the case
entienda lo que quiera pero pero el caso
of dogs I still think that there are
de los perros Yo sigo opinando que hay
dogs and dogs there are dogs that a
perros y perros hay perros que un
positive stimulus is worth But if you have
estímulo positivo vale Pero si tú tienes
a pitbull if you have one I think like that I mean I
un pitbull si tú tienes un yo pienso así
understand that it will depend on the
O sea yo entiendo que dependerá del
animal but There are some That are not going to
animal pero Hay alguno Que no te va a
pay attention to you and you are not going to and you are not going to
hacer caso y no lo vas a y no te vas a
make yourself respected and you are not going to educate it with
hacer respetar y no lo vas a educar con
a treat because we are talking about
una golosina es que estamos hablando de
animals in the end and I think there is a
animales al final y creo que hay una
very big difference between making yourself
diferencia muy grande entre hacerte
respected hitting it eh or or hitting it with
respetar pegarle un toque eh o o o darle
a newspaper in the snout like
un periodicazo en el hocico como le ha
Fran gave this afternoon to delox okay Well
dado Fran esta tarde a delox vale Bueno
here now we are going to see the clip okay Javi
aquí ahora vamos a ver el clip vale Javi
handsome can you send a greeting to a
guapo le puedes mandar un saludo a un
friend his name is rare Kid and he's a fan of yours his
colega se llama rare Kid y es fan tuyo
name is what I can't see the text it's too
se llama qué no veo el texto está muy
small reit if you could put it in the
pequeño reit si me lo podéis poner en el
chat we can say hello okay I mean
chat lo saludamos vale o sea
no I think it's mistreatment everyone is
no yo creo que un maltrato todo el mundo
clear about what mistreatment is not
tenemos claro lo que es un maltrato no
mistreatment it's well a beating but a
maltrato es pues una paliza pero una
literal beating you don't know I mean mistreatment
paliza literal no sabes o sea maltrato
FR has always been a fraud with
FR siempre ha sido un fraude con los
animals that was said by delox this was said by
animales eso lo dijo delox esto lo dijo
delox Fran has always been a fraud with
delox Fran siempre ha sido un fraude con
animals and like that was said by delox no
los animales y como eso lo dijo del no
but yes I can be a fraud I can
pero sí que puedo ser un fraude Yo puedo
be a fraud with animals I can be
ser un fraude con los animales puedo ser
a fraud as a person I can be whatever they
un fraude como persona puedo ser lo que
want yeah that doesn't matter to me I mean him
quieran si que a mí eso me da igual o
telling me that I'm a
sea que me diga delos a mí que yo soy un
fraud is like a parody it's
fraude es como una parodia es como es
like if he tells me Dallas that I get
como si me dice a mí Dallas que me pongo
aggressive on the internet it's the same No
agresivo en internet es lo mismo No
better it's as if sasel calls you bald he does
mejor es como si sasel te llama calvo
n't send balls dude we already saw this one that
no manda huevazos tío este ya lo vimos
is the clip before you a rottweiler
que es el clip de antes ti un rottweiler
eh This ent is very good training it with
eh Está muy bien este ent entrenarlo con
positive encouragement but those dogs
estímulo positivo pero a esos perros
Precisely  you have to train them so
Precisamente hay que entrenarlos para
that when your voice sounds calling
que cuando tu voz suene delo llamando
someone a fraud man he has Mao
fraude a alguien tío es que tiene Mao
rare kit rare kit worth a kiss rare kit
rare kit rare kit vale un beso rare kit
in a hard way the dog says [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm
de una manera dura el perro diga [__]
not moving because they are dogs that
[__] no me muevo porque son perros que
are potentially dangerous or a
son potencialmente peligrosos o un perro
small dog can be potentially
pequeño puede ser potencialmente
dangerous a chihuahua can be a
peligroso un chihuahua puede ser un
potentially dangerous dog that if you don't
perro potencialmente peligroso que si no
have authority with the dog it can
tienes autoridad con el perro le puede
bite a child I mean there's something
morder a un niño es decir hay una cosa
called authority with animals
que se llama autoridad con los animales
and we're forgetting that animals
y se nos está olvidando que los animales
are animals and dogs are not
son animales y los los perros no son
cats I say this because a lot of people compare them
gatos lo digo porque mucha gente compara
with cats No I taught my cat
con los gatos No yo a mi gato le enseñé
to your cat You taught it because it has
a tu gato Le enseñaste porque tiene unas
different characteristics and it goes by
características diferentes y va por unos
different smells but the dog is
olores diferentes pero el perro va
marking so eh [ __ ] it's important
marcando entonces eh [__] es importante
that people understand that when you say
que la gente entienda que cuando se dice
that you have to eh hit a
que hay que eh darle una [__] a un
dog it's not that you're going to kill it it's that you have
perro no es que lo vas a matar es que lo
to train it so that if at a
tienes que entrenar para que si en un
given moment you tell it to stop, don't cross
momento dado le dices para no te cruce
a road and a car hits it, so that the
una carretera y lo pille un coche que el
dog understands you, you can't tell it to stop
perro te entienda no le puedes decir
and have a treat to give it so
para y tener una chuche Para darle para
that  stop then a lot of people here talk
que pare entonces mucha gente aquí habla
about no because now
de no porque ahora el entrenamiento
positive training is what the
positivo es lo que dicen los
Cali trainers say that yes yes
entrenadores calinos que sí que sí que
positive training but crazy crazy crazy
entrenamiento positivo pero loco loco
crazy they are here dude yes always eh but it's
loco loco están aquí tío sí siem eh pero
not that one is there it's that one is there and the
no es que esté uno es que está uno y el
other one who is challenging of course they are
otro que está retando claro están aquí
both here mother of my life I have
los dos madre de mi vida tengo
arguments I have proof I have
argumentos tengo pruebas tengo
credibility no no but it's that this is the one
credibilidad no no pero es que este es
from telesalseo before they are sick they
el de telesalseo de antes son enfermos
are sick Look I mean they are
son enfermos Mira o sea son enfermos
completely sick completely sick I
completamente enfermos completamente o
mean in the telesalseo live and now they have
sea en el directo de telesalseo y ahora
come for this yes yes yes Ju
se han venido para este sí sí sí Ju
watching it in real time and clicking
viéndolo a tiempo real y poniendo click
in real time you don't have that moment
a tiempo real tú no tienes ese momento
of the treat to give the [ __ ] dog
de la chuche para darle al [__] perro
when there is a road it is going to cross it
cuando hay una carretera va a cruzarla
a car throws at it and you say [ __ ] the
le tira un coche y dices [__] el
positive training on the other hand if you
entrenamiento positivo en cambio si le
tell it to stay and the dog stops it is
dices quieto y el perro se para está
saving a life or it is going to go for a
salvando la vida o se va a ir a por un
child or it is biting it and says
niño o le está mordiendo y le dice
release it has learned to release because there are
suelta ha aprendido a soltar porque hay
training centers where they do not
centros de entrenamiento donde no te
let you see how they train the dogs I mean that's how it is
dejan ver cómo entrenan a los perros o
then a lot of people
sea es que es así entonces mucha gente
who speak speak from the point  from an
que habla habla desde el punto de vista
animalist point of view which is [ __ ] [ __ ] these
animalista que es una [__] [__] estos
days and they have read three articles and two
días y han leído tres artículos y dos
people have told them
personas les han dicho el entrenamiento
positive training is the best thing that the dog is an
positivo Es lo mejor que el perro es un
animal that is a [ __ ] animal at the end
animal que es un [__] animal al final
of the day it does not rationalize things it
del día no racionaliza las cosas
understands better than other animals by
entiende mejor que otros animales por
behaviors by voice by Sound by
comportamientos por voz por Sonido por
smells by situations by attitudes
olores por situaciones por actitudes
but damn the treat thing is very
pero [__] yo lo de la chuche está muy
good, the Oh darling I'll give you a prize
bien lo de Ay cariño Te doy un premio
that no no no if the dog has to
que no que no que si el perro tiene que
stop in front of the road you don't
pararse en frente a una carretera no lo
stop it with a treat or affection you don't
paras con una chuche ni un cariño no lo
stop it I mean you have to have a voice of
paras O sea hay que tener una voz de
authority and that voice of authority is
autoridad Y esa voz de autoridad se
achieved when the dog understands that if it does
consigue cuando entiende el perro que si
not obey that authority it is going to
no obedece aosb de autoridad le va a
get a slap a slap or a punishment
venir una [__] una [__] o un castigo
but as also happens when we have
pero como ocurre también cuando se ha
also talked about raising
hablado también de la crianza de los
children Here people have also
niños Aquí la gente también esto lo
debated this the same chat and
hemos debatido la tertulia igual y la
people take it very very tremendously
gente se lo lleva muy muy a la tremenda
but the child does not get there no you do not have to
pero el niño no llega no no tienes que
hit it ever Not a slap or
llegar a pegarle nunca Ni una [__] ni
a smack or anything like that I mean
una colleja ni nada por el estilo o sea
the child does understand if you talk to it
el niño sí entiende con que tú le hables
serious or that you scold him seriously do you
serio o que tú le riñes serio me
understand me I don't know that it's a
entiendes a no sé que sea un
child's nonsense Why the poor
despropósito de niño Por qué el pobre
kid called nauter eh man no 96 eh if you're
chaval llamado nauter eh tío no 96 eh si
going to be disrespectful man any of those
vas a faltar respeto tío alguno de los
in the discussion like that no man I mean a
de la tertulia así no tío o sea un
joke a joke a criticism Yes okay
chiste un chiste una crítica Sí vale
But that's a bit of an insult a bit
Pero eso es un poco un insulto un poco
of free no so please that doesn't
de de gratis no así que porfa eso no no
hit no I mean no I don't like it when they don't
pega no O sea no no me gusta cuando no
do it to me no or what And my mother
lo hacen a mí no o qué Y ha mi madre más
has slapped me more than once and I do
de una vez me ha dado una cachetada y yo
n't say Oh I'm violent there's a saying that
no digo Ay me violent hay un refrán que
says a good slap in time prevents
dice una buena [__] a tiempo evita
a lot of problems and there's an age at there's
muchos problemas y hay una edad en hay
an age in children when you have to
una edad en los niños cuando le tienes
spank them on the ass eh Because they
que dar un azote en el culo eh Porque
're going to Los Enchufes or because they
está yendo a Los enchufes o porque se
're trying to get into what are you
está intentando meter en el qué sua eres
Javier [ __ ] but if it's that I me I me I
Javier [__] pero si es que me me me me
'm a good guy already eh the water or
soy un buenazo tío ya eh el agua o
because this and that eh It's not hitting
porque esto y lo otro eh No es pegar a
children it's not that you go to school and they
los niños no es que vayas al colegio y
hit you I mean people this
te peguen O sea la gente esta la
nonsense this  of the brats who are
tontería esta de los niñatos que están
on the internet saying Oh this is one of those
en internet diciendo Ah este es de los
who hits their children when they were
que pega a sus hijos cuando eran
little if they had to spank them on
pequeños si había que darles un azote en
the ass they get it because why Because we are
el culo se les da por qué Porque estamos
facing a generation that those who
ante una generación que los que te los
are under 20 or 25 years old
que tien menos de 20 años o 25 años hoy
today, okay, hey, you who are 24, 25
en día vale eh cel tú que tienes 24 25
years old, you have to have friends who are
años tú tienes que tener amigos que son
[ __ ] [ __ ] who are not even worth
una [__] [__] que no valen ni para
taking in the ass because they have been taught
tomar por culo porque les han enseñado
that life is [ __ ] and that everything has to be
que la vida es una [__] y que todo
given to you and such and such,
tienen que dártelo y que tal y que es
look, they are abusing me and you
que fijat que me están abusando y tú lo
know it, it is a generation that is not made of
sabes es una generación que no es de
glass it is a weak generation and it is
cristal es una generación débil y es
because everything has been taught to them With a
porque todo se les ha enseñado Con
reward in a positive way, then you
premio de manera positiva entonces tú te
[ __ ] a kid who came from the
coges a un chaval que ha salido de las
streets of Cambodia, a kid who
calles de cambodia un chaval que ha
came from Spain and that kid from the
salido de España y ese chaval de las
streets of Cambodia builds a boat
calles de cambodia te Construye un barco
without having a [ __ ] idea how to build
sin tener ni [__] idea cómo se construy
a boat, you know what I mean, and he, the one who
un barco me entiendes y el el que ha
came from Spain, drowns and commits suicide,
salido de España se ahoga y se suicida
so these are things that many times, as
entonces son cosas que muchas veces como
we are  in this society in which you have to be
estamos en esta sociedad en la cual hay
careful what you say
que tener cuidado de lo que se dice
because if you say something eh [ __ ] be careful no
porque como digas algo eh [__] cuidado
well no you have to be careful you have an
no pues no hay que tener cuidado tú
opinion that's what you think for example
opinas eso lo opinas la por ejemplo la
this girl thought that no no no he he
chica esta opinaba que no no no el el
has to be positive Hey perfect
tiene que ser positivo Oye perfecto
girl It seems perfect to me I made a
chica Me parece perfecto yo te hecho un
video for you because you start by saying I think she's
vídeo porque empiezas diciendo creo que
[ __ ] she thinks I'm [ __ ] I
es subnormal ella cree que soy subnormal
understand that she thinks I'm [ __ ]
entiendo que crea que soy subnormal
Because I live a [ __ ] life and I
Porque vivo una vida de subnormales y
do [ __ ] things I understand okay
hago cosas de subnormal lo entiendo vale
But look I learned something new
Pero mira aprendi una cosa nueva
learned the subject of the Osborne bull
aprendió el tema del del toro de osborne
that has nothing to do with
que no tiene nada que ver con la
bullfighting [ __ ] well dog yes yes he thinks he's going to be
tauromaquia [__] bueno perro si si cree
mistreated I mean when he's
que va a ser maltratado o sea cuando es
considered an object eh eh I'll see him off
considerado un objeto eh eh lo veo fuera
camera another time on the way
de cámaras en otro momento por camino
something no but there's no fight between them or
algo no pero no hay pelea entre ellos o
what everyone knows Dallas you
qué todo el mundo conoce a Dallas le
know him inside out you know when he
conocéis de arriba a abajo sabéis cuá
really threatens and when he's not
amenaza de verdad y cuando no amenaza de
really threatening you know when he's going to file a
verdad sabéis cuánd va a poner una
complaint and when he's not going to file a
denuncia y cuando no va a poner una
complaint you know when he goes You know
denuncia sabéis Cuándo va Lo sabéis
Excuse me  interruption But what good
Disculpa la interrupción Pero qué buenas
tits gbel has raised hand melon melon
lolas tiene gbel mano levantada melón
back of the hand bu has good
melón dorso de la mano bu tiene buenas
tits gbel eh you'll have to see
tetillas el gbel eh habrá que vezas
Oreos then what surprises me
oreos entonces lo que a mí me sorprende
Is that people because of the hatred they
Es que la gente por el odio que le
have for him because of the hatred they have for him which is
tienen por el odio que le tienen que es
normal I understand that there is hatred
normal que entiendo que haya odio no
are not capable of saying [ __ ] It's true
sean capaces de decir [__] Es verdad
that if you beat up a
que si tú le pegas una paliza a un
greyhound puppy or whatever they end up a
cachorro de galgo o sea terminan un
vet Where is the complaint from a
veterinario Dónde está la denuncia de un
vet but it's that apart from that to me the
veterinario pero es que aparte a mí el
issue of the expert reports is that I don't
tema de los peritajes es que me da un
really care I mean That sounds very
poco igual de verdad O sea Eso suena muy
good It gives a lot of weight to the matter not
bien Le da mucho peso al asunto no
expert but it's that when you
peritado peritado pero es que cuando tú
hire the expert reports and with this I
el peritajes lo contratas tú y con esto
don't want to e to see nor nor nor am I
no quiero e a ver ni ni ni estoy
saying that they are false or true
diciendo que sean falsas ni verdaderas
or anything I don't get into that okay m
ni nada no me meto en eso vale m
simply that it's not worth it to me I mean no
simplemente que a mí no me vale o sea no
no for me it is never irrefutable proof
no para mí no es una prueba irrefutable
Not a capture or an expert report or
nunca Ni una captura ni un peritaje ni
anything like that I mean in their day they
nada por el estilo o sea en su día
carried an appraisal that said that the
llevaban un aperito que decía que el
dog was the dog was different  do you
perro era el perro era diferente os
remember and that appetizer in the end was
acordáis y ese aperito al final se
thrown back if I'm not
terminó echando para atrás si no me
mistaken So what can I tell you m It's not
equivoco Entonces qué te digo m No es
that it's appraised Okay, very well
que está peritado Vale pues muy bien
but where it's appraised by part it's an
pero dónde está peritado de parte es un
expert from the court what what What do you want to
perito del juzgado qu qué Qué me quieres
tell me and then apart from the conversation being real
contar y ya luego aparte que sea real la
the context eh if
conversación el contexto eh si es
what is being said in those
literal lo que está diciendo en esas
conversations is literal or you don't understand me
conversaciones o no me entiendes
So of course
Entonces claro yo de ciertas personas
I don't believe certain people's things let's say I
pues yo las cosas no me las creo vamos
almost wouldn't
yo ya a día de hoy casi que no me
believe it or I mean it doesn't make sense
creería ni o sea es que no tiene sentido
you know what happened what happened
me entiendes Qué ha pasado qué ha pasado
with that man who was spamming Javi
con ese hombre que estaba spameando Javi
says Rafael if you're going to talk about
dice Rafael que si vas a hablar de los
Dallas' confidentiality agreements
contratos de confidencialidad de Dallas
I see fear what cube But why are
veo miedo el qué cubo Pero por qué están
people so angry at Dallas and
tan la gente que le odian al Dallas y y
to me they're like very bad man Look if you could
a mí son como muy malitos tío Mira si tú
see how they were putting it there in the
vieres cómo estaban poniendo allí en el
chat in the sele chat how they
chat al en el chat de sele cómo los
were putting it to everyone man I mean I
estaban poniendo a todos tío O sea me
imagine that it can be recovered if you
imagino que se podrá recuperar si tú los
see them I don't know if if I left it uploaded they
Ves Es que no sé si s lo dej subido lo
explain it Where  there is the complaint of such
expliquen Dónde está la denuncia de tal
then they present a conversation of a
luego presentan una conversación de una
neighbor yes yes that one that who has it
vecina sí sí esa eso a quién se lo ha
sent to a conversation of a neighbor
mandado a una conversación de una vecina
eh [ __ ] it I mean the
eh a tomar por culo O sea la
conversation of the neighbor has to be
conversación de la vecina tiene que ser
real it has to be a real neighbor
real tiene que ser una vecina de verdad
and then that the neighbor is not what
y luego que la vecina no sea lo que
they were saying in their day that the
ellos estaban diciendo en su día que la
neighbor hears a scream and I my dog
vecina escucha un grito y yo mi perro
himself you know my dog Javi I have never
mismo sabes mi perro Javi Yo nunca he
seen worse harassers than the ones you
visto mayores acosadores que los que
have no no they are very specialized things
tenéis no no son cositas muy especialita
very very very very bad like that Look there was there
muy muy mu muy malitos así Mira estaba
the creature and eh spamming
estaba la criatura e eh spameando
copying and pasting Pin Pin Pin that if
copiando y pegando Pin Pin Pin que si
I talk about the confidentiality agreements
hablo de los contratos confidencialidad
But what do you want me to talk again about what
Pero qué quieres que hable otra vez lo
we talked about yesterday or or or what
de han que hablamos ayer o o o lo que
delox is saying that with that
está diciendo delox que ya con eso se
all the confidentiality agreements have been broken
han roto todos los contratos de
that no I don't know the truth
confidencialidad que no no sé la verdad
friend that then years later he
amiga que luego años más tarde ha
saved that message so that he stops it for him you
guardado ese mensaje para que se lo para
know that the message the
que se lo sabes que el mensaje el
message of some neighbors or in other words they are
mensaje de la de unos vecinos o sea son
some messages from some neighbors from that time
unos mensajes de unos vecinos de aquel
a conversation of a neighbor
entonces una conversación de una vecina
with another neighbor from that time now
con otra vecina de aquel entonces ahora
that I don't know no what I tell you what I tell you what it
que no sé no qué te digo qué Te digo qu
is  that or rather first where the [ __ ] does
es eso o sea primero de dónde [__] sale
that chat come from and then m And then what about Tyrion
ese chat y luego m Y luego qué el tyrion
Tyrion many times you scold him or
el tyrion muchas veces tú le rines o le
take something off him that or rather you take something off him
quitas algo que o sea le quitas algo de
eh yesterday for example he had some of
eh ayer por ejemplo tenía un maquillaje
my daughter's makeup in his mouth some foam Okay and I
de mi hija en la boca una espuma Vale y
went to take it off his mouth or rather zero
se la fui a quitar de la boca o sea cero
aggression or rather like how I am super
agresividad o sea así como yo soy super
light and talking to him and he yells at me
light y hablándole y me pega un chillido
my dog is an idiot you understand what
mi perro está [__] me entiendes
I'm saying [ __ ] I [ __ ] on my [ __ ] life
que yo digo [__] me cago en mi [__] vida
a neighbor was really hitting me in the ass
una vecina me daba mucho por el culo
because my dog howled no No mine no he doesn't
porque mi perro aullaba no No el mío no
howl maybe he can bark if
no aulla a lo mejor puede ladrar si
someone comes home like my father or
viene alguien a casa en plan mi padre o
something but suddenly yell
algo así pero de repente chillar por
please give him the glass of milk now and go to
favor darle ya el vasito de leche y a
sleep to grandpa no Jessica I gave him to
dormir al abuelo no Jessica lo di a
Miare and so that he doesn't stay because the
miare y para que no se quede porque la
neighbor Then he became friends Look look look
vecina Luego se hizo a amig Mira mira
eh or rather me Show me evidence
mira eh o sea a mí Preséntame pruebas
of animal abuse and the only
del del maltrato al animal y las únicas
evidence this girl has presented are
pruebas que ha presentado esta chica son
some wounds caused by mange that's the
unas heridas provocadas por sarna es lo
only thing she has  taught this girl has not
único que ha enseñado esta chica no ha
shown a tear, a wound, an
enseñado una rotura una herida una
inflammation, a vet report has not
inflamación un reporte veterinario no ha
presented anything What happens is that the
presentado nada Lo que pasa es que los
idiots on the internet, okay, eh, they believe it and that's why they
lerdos de internet vale eh se lo creen y
gave the dog to Dallas, that's why they
por eso le han dado al perro al Dallas
gave the dog to Dallas because
por eso le dan el perro al Dallas porque
judicially that is not worth it, that is worth it to you
no judicialmente eso no vale eso te vale
for the internet funa and for the people
para la funa de internet y para la gente
who are against it But that is not worth it
que est en contra Pero eso no vale
judicially, everything but of course a judge
judicialmente todo pero claro un juez
presents Hey, give me proof What evidence have you
presenta Oye Dame prue Qué pruebas me
presented to me this and this and this, the
has presentado esto y esto y esto el
judge What does he say? Hey girl, we are in a
juez Qué dice Oye chica estamos en un
courtroom This is not the internet, that's what
juzgado Esto no es internet eso es lo
happens, that then you go around as an animal rights activist and you
que pasa que luego vayas de animalista y
go to the animal rights groups and you
te vayas con los grupos animalistas y
say this and that, it seems very good to me but
digas tal y cual me parece muy bien pero
where there is no abuse there is no abuse, I
donde no hay maltrato no hay maltrato o
mean, where there is no abuse there is no
sea donde no hay maltrato no hay
abuse and I have not seen a [ __ ] photo
maltrato y yo no he visto una [__] foto
of that dog, not inflamed, nor with blood,
de ese perro ni inflamado ni con sangre
nor with a tear, nor a
ni con una rotura ni un reporte
vet report, nor a no, the only
veterinario ni un no el único reporte
vet report out there is a
veterinario que hay por ahí es cambio de
chip change, Eh, This, the other, I mean, be careful, be careful
Chip Eh Esto lo otro o sea cuidado
because here it is And the thing is that there is nothing else, I
cuidado que aquí lo Y es que no hay más
mean, there is nothing else That's  what there is,
nada O sea no hay más nada Eso es lo que
those who have committed a crime are
hay los que han cometido un delito son
them, I mean, as I tell you, and now it is
ellos o sea como te lo digo y ahora yo
not known if it is Carlos Parlos or his [ __ ]
no se sabe si es Carlos parlos o su [__]
mother, that is the story and this
madre eso esa es la historia y este
trial that now comes out like this, this trial
juicio que ahora salen así este juicio
is why the judge provisionally
es por eso que el juez cautelarmente
said return the dog to Dallas, it
haya dicho devuélvele el perro a Dallas
is because seeing the plan it
es porque es porque viendo el plan no
has nothing to do with it, it has to do with because
tiene nada que ver tiene que ver porque
obviously it is the second time that it is
obviamente es que es la segunda vez que
pitiful there, it is the second time and it
des pena ahí es que es la segunda vez y
is that they are seeing the plan, man, the
es que están viendo el plan hombre el
dog is passing by its years, you know Ian, it is that
perro van pasando sus años sabes Ian es
I no longer know how to explain
que ya es que yo ya no sé cómo explicar
to people that Dallas made two
a la gente que Dallas hizo dos
approaches to resolve that problem,
acercamientos para resolver ese problema
two that I know of, two that I know of and I know it, I
dos que yo sepa dos que yo sepa y lo sé
mean, I know it because I have seen it,
es decir lo sé porque yo lo he visto
then I do not know if they have done more and the
luego no sé si habrá hecho más y la
response has been, eh, tururu that I saw you and
respuesta ha sido eh tururu que te vi y
that dog could be there in that house,
ese perro podía estar ahí en esa casa
no, but right now Dallas is saying that he wants to
que no pero si ahora mismo está diciendo
share it and that no, no,
el Dallas de compartirlo y que no que no
that what they want is funaro, which
que ellas lo que quieren es funaro que
is the plan and not to have so many problems,
es el plan y no tener tantos problemas
but let's see in the end that it is resolved, I
pero a ver al final que se resuelva es
mean, I tell you the same thing when  I
decir yo lo mismo te digo cuando yo
close the computer to me marlos parlos
Cierro la computadora a mí marlos parlos
and their [ __ ] mother I don't give a [ __ ] like
y su [__] madre Me una [__] como a
everyone else, I mean, people are
todo el mundo es decir la gente está
dismayed, that dog, where is that dog going to go,
consternada ese perro dónde va a ir ese
for God's sake, but then people don't give
perro por Dios pero luego la gente le
a [ __ ] [ __ ]. Hey, any
importa una [__] [__] Eh cualquier
dog, any cat, and any person, I
perro cualquier gato y cualquier persona
mean, we are [ __ ] hypocrites,
es decir Somos unos [__] hipócritas la
people Big boss, you already reacted to the
gente Big boss tú ya reaccionaste a los
Peruvians by swearing at streamers What is that?
peruanos funando streamers Qué es eso
Thank you very much, friend. Hey, I just
Muchas gracias amigo Oye me acabo de dar
realized that we have 19 super chats with 50
cuenta que llevamos 19 super chat de 50
and 100 new members, people. It's hypocritical, I
y 100 miembros nuevos gente Es hipócrita
mean, it can't be. We have to help. We
o sea es que no puede ser hay que ayudar
have to help. Why are you going to help,
hay que ayudar per qué vas a ayudar tú
you [ __ ]? Look at what
subnormal tú mírate lo que están
these people are saying. Ask your mother for the
diciendo estos Pídele a tu madre los los
10 so you can go out and go out on the street, you
10 para poder salir y vete a la calle
[ __ ]. I mean, there you go. The dog is
retrasada o sea ya está el perro se le
ashamed of people, but people on both
apena a la gente pero la gente tanto de
sides, eh, I mean,
un bando como del otro eh o sea eso
absolutely not. People want to see the
absolutamente no la gente quiere ver al
dog in Dubai running on the beach and
perro en Dubai por la playa corriendo y
Dallas crying with emotion or what's up, my
Dallas llorando de emoción o qué pasa mi
tesa. You're here too. Well, there are already
tesa estás por aquí también pues ya son
20.  I don't know, I don't know if I'm going to hold out to
20 yo no sé no sé si voy a aguantar para
record the video for the main channel, it's
grabar el vídeo del Canal principal son
3:15 but I'm falling down, the thing
las 3:15 pero estoy que me caigo lo que
is, I think I'm going to, I think I'm going to
pasa es que creo que voy a creo que voy
make myself a coffee and I'm going to record uh
a hacerme un café y lo voy a grabar eh
another video for the main channel
otro vídeo para el canal principal
apart from the one you have in the morning
aparte el que tenéis por la mañana
because if not I won't take it off and because and
porque si no no me lo quito y porque y
because tomorrow I want when I wake up he's
porque mañana quiero cuando me despierte
with him with the kid all day and
está con el con el canijo todo el días y
now if I have to start recording a video he
ya si me tengo que poner a grabar vídeo
wants to see me with the dog in
quiere ver a mi con el perro en
Czechoslovakia which no longer exists uh
checoeslovaquia que ya no existe eh
walking the dog and saying I did
paseando con el perro y diciendo hecho
everything for my dog people want that and
todo por mi perro la gente quiere eso y
then we all don't give a [ __ ] we all don't give a
luego nos importa una [__] [__] a
[ __ ] what's going on, of
[__] que pasa que cas
course it's gossip it's a movement and they'll go on
claro es salseo es movida y irán a las
television now and Antena 3 will appear
televisiones ahora y aparecerán Antena 3
Oh, it's taking me by proxy
Ay es que me lleva violencia vicaria
but if you give me what you want, go [ __ ] yourself, he's
pero si danas lo que quieres que te
told you
vayas a tomar por culo te lo ha dicho
a thousand times I've heard it I've
mil veces que yo lo he escuchado que yo
heard it leave me alone delete
lo he escuchado déjame en paz borramos
everything leave everything remove everything it's
todo dejamos todo quitamos todo se acabó
all over  and the answer is tururu Of course
todo y La respuesta es tururu Claro
because what they want is to desecrate him and for
porque lo que quieren es funaro a él y
him to be believed and for him to be believed but
que le crean y que que que crean su pero
girl Well then that's it Well look you
chica Bueno pues ya está Pues mira tú
have your version you have your point of
tienes tu versión tú tienes tu punto de
view so keep it to yourself but Live
vista pues quédatela para ti pero Vive
life quietly live quietly and happy
la vida tranquila vive tranquila y feliz
Hey there's this we have to share this
Oye hay un esto hay que compartirlo esto
is something that there's no other way to
es una cosa que no hay otra manera de
do it Okay but no no no no they
hacerlo Vale pero no no no no que
want the entire Internet and
quieren que todo Internet y todo el
everyone to believe him that that d is an
mundo le crean que que que d es un
abuser murderer and the
maltratador asesino y todo el código
entire penal code And the thing is that it's not going to stop it's
penal entero Y es que eso no va a parar
not going to happen There will be people who don't like him
no va a pasar Habrá gente a la que le
but on this issue it doesn't
caiga mal pero en en el tema de este no
change even with the haters that
cambia ni aun con los hater que tiene
Dallas has this year eh with what's
Dallas en este año eh con lo que ha
happened with Pam and all the nonsense there's
pasado con lo de Pam y todo el rollo que
been a lot a lot of hate well not even with
ha habido mucho mucho odio pues ni con
that is it worth it you understand nor getting together
esas les vale me entiendes ni juntándose
with all the haters not of him but of
con todos los hater ya no de él sino de
mine mine Tania the Planas the this one the
mío mío la Tania el planas el este el
other one who no [ __ ] well Live life well
otro que no [__] pues Vive la vida bien
the years go by and why lose it
que los años pasa y y para qué perderlo
you know Well you see it all here
sabes Bueno lo veis ustedes aquí entero
because I'm not going to  see more than me Eh I
porque yo no voy a ver más que me Eh
want to see it wool before I go I
quiero verlo da lana antes de irme
want to see it wool There you'll see a
quiero verlo de lana Ahí va a ver un
little bit of this but it's that Z Z
poquito esto pero es que es que Z Z a
is I don't know what This is a girl who
sea no sé qué Esta es una chica que
says that d you wanted a threesome with
cuenta que d las querías un trío con
her what I tell you girl and turboplus
ella que te digo chica e turboplus
move eye what it says here this
movida ojito lo que dice aquí esta
Twitter account called Javi El
cuenta de Twitter que se llama Javi El
pelucas says I find it incredible the
pelucas dice Me parece increíble la
cowardice of the big streamers
cobardía de los streamers grandes
came out to collaborate and spread the word to
salieron a colaborar y dar difusión para
pay for Frank Cuesta's divorce but
pagarle el divorcio a Frank cuesta pero
not one has come out to support or even
ni uno ha salido a apoyar o aunque sea
mention that Dallas the biggest
mencionar lo de que Dallas el mayor
piece of [ __ ] on the internet recovers a dog that he
[__] de internet recupere un perro que
abused I wonder why it is that
maltrataba me pregunto por qué será por
the streamers don't want to support
lo que los streamers no quieren apoyar
this case not because they don't believe it Turbo
este caso no porque no se lo creen Turbo
plan my son the worst of all is that
plan hijo mío lo peor de todo es que
this is just the tip of the ice see No I ca
esto es solo la punta de elice ver No yo
n't take it anymore come on Let's go let's go let's
no puedo más venga Vámonos vámonos
go V hostia kelin posted this
vámonos V [__] kelin ha puesto esto
what's going on It bores me to
qué está pasando Me aburre hasta el
infinity that they come back again and again with the
infinito que vuelvan una y otra vez con
same thing from 10 years ago very fed up of
lo mismo de hace 10 años muy harta de
living it from the shelter and  put up with
vivirlo desde el burladero y aguantar
calls from a jerk who swears she wo
llamadas de una impresentable que me jur
n't stop until she sees my
que no va a parar hasta que vea a mi
son in jail She tried with
hijo en la cárcel Lo intentó con
lies man This gives me the impression that she's going to get
mentiras buah Esto me da a mí que se va
more heated eh I mean Dallas's mother
a encender más eh o sea la madre del
already in full force says a jerk who
Dallas ya a saco dice una impresentable
called her on the phone to
que le que la llamó por teléfono para
tell her she won't stop until she sees
decirle que no va a parar hasta que vea
my son in jail and she tried with
a mi hijo en la cárcel y lo intentó con
lies man my god my god I wanted to
mentiras tío madre mía madre mía quería
see about the hitmen but I'm
ver lo de los sicarios pero lo de los
going to do the hitmen thing tomorrow luar
sicarios lo voy a hacer mañana luar
write down the hitmen for tomorrow
apúntame los de los sicarios para mañana
luare foreign
luare foreign
[Music]
[Música]